Guide to the Edwin Robert Anderson Seligman papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Edwin Robert Anderson Seligman Papers,
[ca. 1750]-1939
Seligman, Edwin R. A. (Edwin Robert Anderson), 1861-1939.
48 linear ft. (ca. 52,700 items in 111 boxes; 25 volumes; 3 unbound volumes).
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
4079598
Biographical Note
Columbia A.B. 1879; A.M. 1884; L.L.B. 1884; Ph.D. 1885; L.L.D. 1904. Seligman served on the Columbia University faculty 1885-1931; the Tax Committee of New York City 1914-1916 and of New York State 1929-1931; the League of Nations committee on economics and finance 1922-1923; financial advisor to Cuba in 1931; editor of the Political Science Quarterly and the Encyclopedia of Social Sciences, among many other roles.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, manuscripts and documents. Included among his personal and professional correspondence are letters from famous economists collected by Seligman. Among these are: I) William Shirley (Box 95). 1741-1745. Copies of letters and documents by Shirley, Royal Governor of Massachusetts, addressed chiefly to the Board of Trade, London; II) Paul Flobart (Box 96). Recherches sur les Billets de la Banque de Law, 1716-1720. Lille, 1920. Notes, page proof and printed for of this pamphlet; III) John Francis Bray Papers (Box 97). Bray, 1809-1895, early socialist writer and labor agitator in England, 1822, returned to America in 1842. Michigan experiences, 1842-1896, papers 1860-1890; IV) Ernest Jones Papers. Correspondence, family and business papers of Ernest Jones, 1819-1869, English militant socialist and leader of the Chartist movement, and publisher of two newspapers propagating Marxist doctrines. Collection consists of ca.1,708 items, and some family correspondence and mementoes. The most valuable part appears to be his notes refuting various libel charges brought against him. In 10 boxes at the end of the collection.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 6 series:
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Arranged Files
Series III: Printed Material
Series IV: Scrapbooks
Series V: John Frances Bray Papers
Series VI: Ernest Charles Jones Papers, 1819-1969
Subjects
Columbia University--Faculty.; League of Nations--Finance.; New York (N.Y.).--Tax Commission.; New York (State).--State Tax Commission.; Ashley, W. J. (William James), Sir, 1860-1927.; Clark, John Bates, 1847-1938.; Edgeworth, Francis Ysidro, 1845-1926.; Seligman, Edwin R. A. (Edwin Robert Anderson), 1861-1939.; Marshall, Alfred, 1842-1924.; Taussig, F. W. (Frank William), 1859-1940.; Walras, Léon, 1834-1910.; Cuba.; Economics--Study and teaching.; Economics--History.; Econometrics.; Bibliographies.; Bills (financial).; Card catalogs.; Notebooks.; Photographs.; Portraits.; Reports.; Scrapbooks.; College teachers.; Economists.; Editors.
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
The following boxes are located on-site: Series I: Correspondence and Series VI: Ernest Charles Jones Papers.
The following boxes are located off-site: 1-116. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Acquisition
Papers Purchase, 1929 & 1942
Alternate Formats
Ernest Charles Jones papers; James Bryce correspondence; Sir William James Ashley letters are on microfilm.
"Knies-Volkswirthschaftslehre," 1881, bound manuscript lecture notebook in Seligman's hand, 64 p., from Box 86 is on microfilm [#2005-7014]
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries I.1: Cataloged
    - Abbey, Edwin Austin
    - Abbott, Lawrence Fraser
    - Abbutt, Lyman
    - Adams, Charles Francis
    - Adams, Henry Carter
    - Adams, Thomas, S.
    - Addams, Jane
    - Adler, Cyrus
    - Adler, Felix
    - Aftalion, Albert
    - Agger, Eugene Ewald
    - Albee, Edward F.
    - Alger, Hiratio, Jr.
    - Allison, William Boyd
    - Anderson, Benjamin McAlester, Jr.
    - Anderson, Edward Hatfield
    - Anderson, Mary R.M.
    - Anderson, Thomas Davis
    - Andrew, Abram Piatt
    - Andrews, Charles Mclean
    - Andrews, E. Benjamin
    - Angell, James Haterhouse
    - Angell, James Howalnd
    - Angell, Jane N.
    - Ashley, Sir William James
    - Atkinson, Edward
    - Aulnis de Bourouill, J.
    - Babson, Roger
    - Baker, Bernard Nadel
    - Baker, Charles Whiting
    - Baldwin, William Henry, Jr.
    - Bancroft, Frederic
    - Banks, Enoch Marvin
    - Bannister, Lucius Ward
    - Baring, Sir Francis
    - Barnard, Frederick Augustus Porter
    - Barnard, George Grey
    - Barnes, Harry Elmer
    - Barnes, Julius Howland
    - Barone, Enrico
    - Barrault, Emile
    - Barrett, Robert
    - Barrows, David P.
    - Baruch, Bernard M.
    - Bastable Charles Francis
    - Battle, George Gordon
    - Bauer, Stephen
    - Beard, Charles A.
    - Bechaux, Auguste
    - Bellom, Maurice
    - Bemis, Edward Webster
    - Bender, Albert Maurice
    - Bender, Harold Herman
    - Benson, Roberty Dix
    - Bergson, Henri
    - Berkeley, George, Bishop of Cloyns
    - Bernays, Edward L.
    - Beveridge, Albert Jeremiah
    - Bixby, William Keeney
    - Blair, Henry William
    - Blanshard Paul
    - Bliss, William Dwight Porter
    - Bliven, Bruce
    - Blunden, L.H.
    - Boas, Franz
    - Bodio, Luigi
    - Bogart, Ernest L.
    - Bogert, Marston Tayloe
    - Bohm-Bawerk, Eugen von
    - Boisservain, G.M.
    - Bolles, Albert S.
    - Bonar, James
    - Bonbright James Cummings
    - Borah, William E.
    - Boucke, Oswald Fred
    - Bourne, Edward Gaylord
    - Bowker, R.R.
    - Brandeis, Louis Dembitz
    - Breckenridge, Roeliff Morton
    - Brentano Lujo
    - Brett, george Platt
    - Brinton, Clarence Crane
    - Brookings, Robert Somers
    - Brooks, John Graham
    - Brown, Elmer Ellsworth
    - Brown, Francis Shunk
    - Bruce, E. Marion (Mrs. James)
    - Bruere, Henry
    - Brunner, Arnold William
    - Bryce, James
    - Bullock, Charles J.
    - Burbank, Luther
    - Burgess, John William
    - Burns, John
    - Burt, Thomas
    - Burton, Theodore Elijah
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray
    - Cadwalader, John Lambert
    - Cairns, Huntington
    - Caldwell, Robert J.
    - Calhoun George Miller
    - Canby Henry Seidel
    - Canfield Cass
    - Cannan, Edwin
    - Cardozo, Benjamin Nathan
    - Carnegie, Andrew
    - Carpenter, Willaim Henry
    - Carver, T.N.
    - Cather, Willa
    - Cattell, J McKeen
    - Cecil, Robert
    - Celler, Emanuel
    - Chaddock, Robert Emmet
    - Chailley, Joseph
    - Chalmers, Thomas
    - Champney, James Wells
    - Chapin, Roy D.
    - Chapman, John Jay
    - Chapman, S.C.
    - Chapman, Sydney
    - Chase, Stuart
    - Chevalier, Michel
    - Cheyney, Edward P
    - Childs, Richard Spencer
    - Chisholm, Hugh Joseph
    - Choate, Joseph Hodges
    - Cholmeley-Jones, Richard Oilder
    - Clapham, J.H.
    - Clark, John Bates
    - Clark, John Maurice
    - Clark, Walter E.
    - Cleveland, Frederick Albert
    - Cobden, Richard
    - Cochran, Charles Fremont
    - Coghlan, J.A.
    - Cohn, Gustav
    - Coit, Stanton
    - Colbert, J.B.
    - Colby, Bambridge
    - Colby, James Fairbands
    - Cole, Frand Nelson
    - Cole, Thomas Casilear
    - Collings, Harry Thomas
    - Commons, J.R.
    - Comstock, Alzada
    - Conant, Charles Arthur
    - Conrad, Johannes
    - Conway, Eustace
    - Conway, W.M.
    - Cook, Albert Stanburrough
    - Cort van der Linden, R.W.A.
    - Cortelyou, George Bruce
    - Cossa, Luigi
    - Costigan, Edward P
    - Coudert, Frederic Rene
    - Couzens, James
    - Coykendall, Frederick
    - Crampton, Henry E.
    - Croly, Herbert
    - Crook, J.W.
    - Cross, Ira Brown
    - Cross, Wilber Lucius
    - Crowell, John Franklin
    - Crowninshield, Frank
    - Crowther, Samuel
    - Cunliffe, John William
    - Cunningham, William
    - Curtis, George William
    - Cutting, Robert Fulton
    - D Melvil
    - Dalla Volta, Richard
    - Damrosch, Walter
    - Dana, Richard Henry
    - Dana, Richard Henry
    - Davenport, Frederick Morgan
    - Davenport, Frederick Morgan
    - Davies, Julien Tappan
    - Davies, Julien Tappan
    - Davis, Andrew McFarland
    - Davis, Andrew McFarland
    - Davis, John William
    - De Ford Miriam Allottt
    - De Forest, R.W.
    - De Kay, Charles
    - De Leon, Daniel
    - De Leon, Daniel
    - Dean, Bashford
    - Dean, Bashford
    - Dell, Floyd
    - Deming, Horace Edward
    - Deming, Horace Edward
    - Denis, H.
    - Denis, H.
    - Dent, J.N.
    - Dent, J.N.
    - Deschamps, Auguste
    - Desehamps, Auguste Dewey, Davis Rich
    - Dewey, David Rich
    - Dewey, John
    - Dewey, John
    - Dewey, Melvil
    - Dickinson, G.L.
    - Dickinson, Sidney E
    - Dickinson, Sidney E.
    - Diehl, Karl
    - Diehl, Karl
    - Dixon, Frank Haigh
    - Dixon, Frank Haigh
    - Dodd, Samuel C.T
    - Dodd, Samuel C.T.
    - Doten, Carroll Warren
    - Douglas, Paul Howard
    - Droppers, Garrett
    - Du Bois, W.E.B.
    - du Pont, Pierre Samuel
    - Duboc, Julius
    - Duckworth, A.
    - Duggan, S.P.H.
    - Dulles, Eleanor L.
    - Dulles, John Foster
    - Dunbar, Clarles F
    - Duncan, William Butler
    - Dunning, William Archibald
    - Durand, E. Dana
    - Dutton, George Burwell
    - Easley, Ralph Montgomery
    - Eastman, George
    - Eastwick, William J.
    - Edgeworth, Francis Y.
    - Edwards, George William
    - Eells, Howard Parmelee
    - Einaudi, Luigi
    - Einstein, Albert
    - Eliot, Charles William
    - Elliott, Howard
    - Elliott, John
    - Elliott, T.H.
    - Elwell, Frank Edwin
    - Ely, Richard T.
    - Ely, Robert Erskine
    - Emery, Henry Crosby
    - Erskine, John
    - Espinas, A.
    - Estournelles de Constant, P.
    - Evans, Frederick William
    - F'lagler, Harry H.
    - Fackenthal, Frank D.
    - Fairchild, Fred R.
    - Farnam, Henry W.
    - Farrand, Livingstone
    - Faulkner, Roland P.
    - Feis, Herbert
    - Ferenczi, Sandor
    - Ferguson, John M.
    - Fetter, Frank A.
    - Field, Marshall
    - Finley, John H.
    - Fish, Hamilton
    - Fish, Stuyvesant
    - Fisher, Irving
    - Flagg, Ernest
    - Flagler, Harry H.
    - Flexner, Abraham
    - Flux, A.W.
    - Foerster, F.W.
    - Foldes, Bela
    - Folger, Henry Clay
    - La Follette, Robert M
    - Ford, Franklin
    - Ford, Guy Stanton
    - Ford, James L.
    - Ford, Worthington Chauncy
    - Fosdick, Raymond B.
    - Foskick, Harry Emerson
    - Fox, Austen George
    - Fox, Dixon Rran
    - Foxwell, Herbert Somerton
    - Frame, Andrew Jay
    - France, Joseph Irwin
    - Frank, Glenn
    - Frankfurter, Felix
    - Franklin, Fabian
    - Frear, James A.
    - French, Daniel Chester
    - Freund, Ernst
    - Fried, Hans
    - Frisch, Ragnar
    - Frothingham, Arthur Lincoln
    - Fuller, Harold de Wolf
    - Fuller, Paul Jr.
    - Gabrilowitsch, C.C. & Co.
    - Gale, Zona
    - Gallatin, Albert Eugene
    - Gallinger, Jacob H
    - Gardner Henry B.
    - Garland, Hamlin
    - Garrison, Wendell Phillips
    - Gates, George A
    - Gay, Edwin Francis
    - Gaynor, William Jay
    - George, Annie C.
    - George, Henry
    - Gerard, James W.
    - Gibbins, Henry
    - Gibson, C.D.
    - Giddings, Franklin H.
    - Gide, Charles
    - Giffen, Robert
    - Gilbert, Seymour Parker, Jr.
    - Gilchrist, Huntington
    - Gild Helena (Mrs. Richard Watson)
    - Gilder, Joseph B.
    - Gilder, Richard Watson
    - Gildersleeve, Virginia C.
    - Gilman, Nicholas Paine
    - Gimton, George
    - Gladden, Washington
    - Gladstone, William E.
    - Glass, Carter
    - Glasson, William Henry
    - Godkin, Edwin Lawrence
    - Godwin, William
    - Gompers, Samuel
    - Goodnow, Frank Johnson
    - Goodrich, Caspar Frederick
    - Gore, Thomas P.
    - Goschen
    - Gould, Elgin Ralston Lowell
    - Grady, Henry Francis
    - Grant, Percy Stickney
    - Gray, John H.
    - Gray, Louis Herbert
    - Graziani, Augusto
    - Green, William
    - Green, William Raymond
    - Greene, Belle
    - Greene, E. B.
    - Grew, Joseph Clarke
    - Griffin, Edward Herrick
    - Griffin, Nathaniel Edward
    - Groat, George Gorham
    - Grosvenor, G.H.
    - La Guardia, Fiorello H
    - Gulick, Charles Adams, Jr.
    - Gulick, Luther Halsey
    - Gunton, Amelia (Mrs. George)
    - Guthrie, William Dameron
    - Guyot, Yves
    - Hadley, Arthur Twinning
    - Haensel, Paul
    - Haig, Robert Murray
    - Hale, William Gardner
    - Halle, Ernest von
    - Hamilton, Howland
    - Hamilton, Walton Hale
    - Hammond, Matthew Brown
    - Hamsin
    - Hart, Albert Bushnell
    - Harvey, George
    - Hasback, Wilhelm
    - Hatfield, Henry Rand
    - Hawkes, Herbert Edwin
    - Hawley, Frederick Barnard
    - Haynes, Carlton Joseph Huntley
    - Hays, Arthur G.
    - Hazard, Rowland Gibson
    - Hazlitt, Henry
    - Heer, Clarence
    - Hellman, Geoffrey Theodore
    - Hellman, George Sidney
    - Hepburn, Alonzo Barton
    - Herbert, Victor
    - Herriott, John
    - Herriott, John
    - Herter, Christian
    - Hess, Myra
    - Hewins, William A,B.
    - Hewitt, Abram S
    - Hicks, Frederick C
    - Higgins, Frank Wayland
    - Higgs, Henry
    - Hilles, Charles Dewey
    - Himes, Norman E
    - Hirsch, William W
    - Hirst, Francis W
    - Hobhouse, L.T.
    - Hobson, John A
    - Hodges, Nathaniel Dana Carlile
    - Hollander, Jacob H
    - Holmes, John Haynes
    - Holmes, Oliver W., Jr
    - Holt, Hamilton
    - Holt, Henry
    - Holt, Lucius Hudson
    - Hook, Sidney
    - Hooper, Franklin Henry
    - Hoover, Herbert
    - Hopkins, Edward Washburn
    - Hotchkiss, Willard Eugene
    - Houston, David Franklin
    - Howard, George E
    - Howard, Timothy Edward
    - Howells, William Dean
    - Howland, Fred Arthur
    - Hubbard, Elbert
    - Hughes, Charles Evans
    - Hughes, Thomas
    - Hull, Charles H
    - Hull, Cordell
    - Hullihen, Walter
    - Hume, David
    - Hunt, Edward Eyre
    - Huntington, Archer Milton
    - Huntington, Henry Edwards
    - Hurst, Fannie
    - Ingram, John Kells
    - Isaacs, Stanley M
    - Isaak, A
    - Jackson, Abrahm Valentine Williams
    - James, Edmund J
    - James, William
    - Jameson, John Franklin
    - Jannaccone, P
    - Jannet, Claudio
    - Janschul, Catherine
    - Janschul, Ivan
    - Jaques-Dalcroze, Emile
    - Jay, Pierre
    - Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple
    - Jeze, Gaston
    - Johnson, Allen
    - Johnson, Alvin S
    - Johnson, Edgar A.J.
    - Johnson, Edgar Hutchinson
    - Johnson, Emory R
    - Johnson, Joseph French
    - Johnson, Robert Underwood
    - Johnson, Rossiter
    - Johnston, Alexander
    - Judson, Frederick Newton
    - Jusserand, Jean Adrien Antoine Jules
    - Kahn, Otto Hermann
    - Kaneko, Kentaro
    - Keasbey, Lindley
    - Kelley, Florence
    - Kellogg, Frank Billings
    - Kellogg, Paul U.
    - Kemmerer, E.W.
    - Kennedy, William
    - Keppel, Frederick Paul
    - Keynes, John Maynard
    - Keyser, Cassius Jackson
    - Kinley, David
    - Knies, Karl
    - Knopf, Alfred A
    - Knox, Philander C.
    - Koo, V.K. Wellington
    - Krock, Arthur
    - Kropetkin, Pietro
    - Kuntsford, Viscount
    - Lambeth, Walter
    - Lamont, Hammond
    - Lamont, Thomas William
    - Lamprecht, Karl
    - Landbury, George
    - Lasker, Bruno
    - Lathrop, Francis
    - Lathrop, George Parsons
    - Laughlin, James Laurence
    - Laurier, Wilfrid
    - Laveley, Emile de
    - Lazarus, Emma
    - Leach, Henry G.
    - Leadam, Isaac Saunders
    - Lee, Frederic Schiller
    - Lee, Ivy Ledbetter
    - Lehman, Herbert H
    - Lercy-Beaulieu, Paul
    - Lerner, Max
    - Levasseur, Emile
    - Levy Bruhl, L
    - Levy, Raphael Georges
    - Lewisohn, Adolph
    - Lewisohn, Sam A
    - Leyen, Alfred von der
    - Lichtenberger, James Pendleton
    - Lilienthal, David E.
    - Lindsay, Samuel McCune
    - Lippman, Walter
    - Little, Bascom
    - Liveright, Horace B.
    - Livingston, Arthur
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot
    - Loeb, James
    - Longworth, Nicholas
    - Lord, Herbert Gardiner
    - Loria, Achille
    - Lorwin, Lewis L.
    - Lothian, Philip
    - Love, Robert Alonzo
    - Lovejoy, Arthur O.
    - Lovett, Robert Morse
    - Lovett, Robert Scott
    - Low, Seth
    - Low, William Gilman, Jr.
    - Lowell, Abbott Lawrence
    - Lowell, Josephine S.
    - Luce, Robert
    - Ludlow, John Malcolm
    - Lungren, Fernand
    - Lyon, Hastings
    - Lytton, 3d Earl of
    - Mabie, Hamilton W.
    - MacDonald, J. Ramsay
    - Mack, Julian William
    - Macmillam, F.O.
    - MacVeagh, Franklin
    - MacVeagh, Wayne
    - Macy, Jesse
    - Madariaga, S. de
    - Mahan, Alfred T.
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Malthus, Thomas Robert
    - Mandello, Julius
    - Manes, Alfred
    - Mann, Fritz Karl
    - Manning, William Thomas
    - Marburg, Theodore
    - Marin, Louis
    - Markham, Edwin
    - Marks, Marcus M
    - Marling, Alfred Eeskine
    - Marshall, Alfred
    - Marshall, Henry R.
    - Marshall, Mary P. (Mrs. Alfred)
    - Martin, Alfred Wilhelm
    - Martin, Germain
    - Masaryk, Thomas Garrigue
    - Mason, Alfred Bishop
    - Mason, Arthur Huntington
    - Mason, Daniel Gregory
    - Mastick, Seabury
    - Mather, Frank Jewett, Jr.
    - Matthews, Brander
    - May, Samuel Chester
    - Maye-Snith, Richmond
    - Mayer, Joseph
    - Mayor, James
    - McAdoo, William Gibbs
    - McAnery, George
    - McBain, Howard Lee
    - McClellan, George Brinton
    - McClure, Wallace
    - McCormick, Cyrus H.
    - McCrea, Roswell C
    - McCullock, John Ramsey
    - McLean, George Payne
    - McLean, James
    - McPherson, Logan Grant
    - McRae, Thomas C
    - McVey, Frank LeRond
    - Meeker, Royal
    - Mellon, Andrew William
    - Menger, Carl
    - Merriam, Charles Edward
    - Merritt, Schuyler
    - Menuhin, Yehudi
    - Meyer, Baithasar Henry
    - Meyer, Eduard
    - Michel, Henri
    - Midleton, 1st Earl of
    - Mill, James
    - Miller, Adolph C
    - Miller, Charles R.
    - Miller, Harry E
    - Mills, Frederick C
    - Mills, Ogden Livingston
    - Mills, W.E.
    - Millspaugh, Arthur Chester
    - Mitchell, John
    - Mitchell, John Purroy
    - Mitchell, Lucy Sprague
    - Mitchell, Wesley Clair
    - Moley, Raymond
    - Molton, Robert Russa
    - Monahan, Michael
    - Moody, William Revell
    - Moon, Parker Thomas
    - Moore, Henry L
    - Moore, J.B.
    - Moore, William Underhill
    - More, Paul Elmer
    - Morel-Journel, Henry
    - Morgenthau, Henry
    - Morogues, Baron de
    - Morrison, William Hampson
    - Morrow, Dwight Whitney
    - Moses, Bernard
    - Moses, Montrose J.
    - Moton, Robert Russa
    - Moulton, Harold Glen
    - Mowbray-Clarke, John
    - Mullan, George Vinceny
    - Mumford, Lewis
    - Murray, Gilbert
    - Murrow, Edward R.
    - Mussey, Henry Raymond
    - Mussey, Henry Raymond
    - Muste, A.J.
    - Myeyer, Eugene, Jr
    - Myrdal, Gunnar
    - Nash, John Henry
    - Nathan, C
    - Neale, Edward Vansittart
    - Nearing, Scott
    - Newton, A. Edward
    - Newton, Cahrles B
    - Nicholson, Joseph Shield
    - Nitti, Francesco
    - Nixon, Sir Frank Horsfall
    - Nordhoff, Charles
    - Norman, Montagu
    - North, S.N.D.
    - Northrop, Cyrus
    - Ochs, Adolph S.
    - Ogburn, William Fielding
    - Ogden, Rollo
    - O'Mahoney, Joseph C.
    - Oncken, Auguste
    - Ordway, E.W.
    - Oseroff, Ivan
    - Osborn, Henry Fairfield
    - Osgood, Herbert Levi
    - Oswald, John Clyde
    - Ottinger, Albert
    - Oursler, Fulton
    - Outerbridge, Eugene Harvey
    - Overstreet, H.A.
    - Page, Thomas Walker
    - Page, Walter Hines
    - Paigrave, Robert Harry Inglis
    - Pantaleoni, Maffeo
    - Pareto, Vilfredo
    - Parker, Henry T.
    - Parsons, Elsie C.
    - Parsons, Herbert
    - Parsons, William Barclay
    - Patten, Simon Nelson
    - Payne, Kenneth W.
    - Peabody, George Foster
    - Pearson, Drew
    - Peck, Harry Thurston
    - Peel, Robert
    - Pellew, Henry Edward
    - Pendleton, Ellen F
    - Penrose, Boies
    - Perkins, Frances
    - Peterson, Henry John
    - Pethick-Lawrence, F.
    - Pettengill, Sanuel B
    - Phillippovich, Eugen
    - Phillips, William
    - Pickford, John
    - Pierson, N.G.
    - Pinchot, Gifford
    - Place, Francis
    - Plehn, Carl C
    - Plimpton, George A
    - Plunkett, Horace
    - Polk, Frank Lyon
    - Pope, Arthur Upham
    - Pope, Jesse
    - Posada, Adolfo
    - Pound, Roscoe
    - Powell, Thomas Reed
    - Pratt, Edward Ewing
    - Prendergast, William A
    - Prentice, William K
    - Price, Langford Lovell
    - Prince, John Dyneley
    - Pritchett, Henry Smith
    - Proskauer, Joseph M
    - Pupin, Michael I
    - Purdy, Lawson
    - Putnam, Emily James
    - Putnam, George Haven
    - Putnam, George P.
    - Putnam, Herbert
    - Putnam, Ruth
    - Pyrnne, George
    - Quinn, John
    - Rabbeno, Ugo
    - Rachmaninoff, Sergei Vassilievitch
    - Raffalovich, Arthur
    - Rall, Sidney
    - Reeves, William Pember
    - Reid, Whitelaw
    - Reynolds, James Bronson
    - Ricardo, David
    - Ripley, William Z.
    - Rist, Charles
    - Rives, George Lockhart
    - Robbins, Hayes
    - Roberts, George E
    - Robinson, Leland Rex
    - Rockefeller, John D. Jr.
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
    - Roosevelt, J. R.
    - Roosevelt, Theodore
    - Root, Elihu
    - Roper, Daniel C.
    - Rorty, Malcolm Churchill
    - Roscher, Wilhelm
    - Rosenwald, Julius
    - Ross, Edward A
    - Rowe, Leo
    - Ruml, Beardsley
    - Rylance, Joseph Hine
    - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus
    - Salter, Arthur
    - Salter, William
    - Salvemini, Gaetano
    - Samuel, Herbert
    - Sanger, Margaret
    - Sarnoff, David
    - Satterlee, Herbert Livingston
    - Sax, Emil
    - Saxe, John Godfrey
    - Say, Jean Baptiste
    - Scbmoller, Gustav
    - Schanz, Georg
    - Schieffelin, William Jay
    - Schiff, Jacob Henry
    - Schlesinger, Arthur Meier
    - Schonberg G
    - Schumacher, Hermann
    - Schumpeter, J.A.
    - Schurz, Carl
    - Schuyler, Eugene
    - Schwab, Joseph S
    - Seager, Henry R
    - Sedgwick, Ellery
    - Sedgwick, William Thompson
    - Seitz, Don Carlos
    - Seligman, Edwin R.A.
    - Seligman, Eustace
    - Senior, Nassau William
    - Seward, George
    - Shaw, Albert
    - Shearman, Thomas G
    - Sheffield, T.B. Holroyd, 1st Earl of
    - Shepard, Edward M
    - Sheppard, Morris
    - Sherwell, Guillermo Antoinio
    - Sherwood, Sidney
    - Sherwood, Yates
    - Shortt, Adam
    - Shotwell, James Thomson
    - Shoup, Carl (Sumner)
    - Sibbald, William
    - Sidgwick, Harry
    - Siegfried, Andre
    - Siegfried, Jules
    - Sikes, George Cushing
    - Simiand, F.J.C.
    - Simkovitch, Vladimir
    - Sinclair, Upton
    - Singer, Isidore
    - Sloan, Alfred P.
    - Sloane, William Mulligan
    - Smart, William
    - Smith, Adam
    - Smith, Afired Emanuel
    - Smith, Chhrles Sprague
    - Smith, David Eugene
    - Smith, Francis Asbury
    - Smith, Henry Preserved
    - Smith, Munroe
    - Snavely, Tipton Ray
    - Sombart, Werner
    - Sorokin, P A
    - Spahr, Charles B
    - Spargo, John
    - Speyer, James
    - Spingarn, Joel Elias
    - Stamp, Josiah C.
    - Steel-Maitland, A.
    - Stein, Gertrude
    - Stephano, C
    - Sterne, Simon
    - Stetson, Francis Lynde
    - Stimson, Henry Lewis
    - Stirling, James
    - Stokes, J.G.P.
    - Stolberg, Benjamin
    - Stone, Harlan F.
    - Stopes, Marie C.
    - Stourm, Rena
    - Strachey, Amy S.
    - Strachey, John St.L.
    - Straus, Jesse Isidor
    - Straus, Isidor
    - Straus, Oscar S.
    - Strauss, Anna Lord
    - Sullivan, Mark
    - Sulzberger, A.H.
    - Sulzberger, C.L.
    - Sumner, William Graham
    - Suranyi-Tinger, Theo
    - Suret, Louis
    - Sutherland, Douglas
    - Sutherland, William A
    - Swift, Louis F.
    - Swope, Herbert B.
    - Swope, Gerard
    - Taft, Lorado